okay let's try making a nanotape
squishmallow squishy I've been obsessed
with making these lately so I first
added some pink paint into some water
and mixed it in then I got some Nano
tape and to make it easier I usually
tape the ends together with washi tape
this is my original method so I shall
call this minori method peel it off and
cut off some excess then with pasta
paint pen I added some decorations a
white belly and then extra parts on
extra tape again it's my method but I
added tape over it to seal it in place
let's cut it up into small pieces and
add it onto the balloon the ball itself
is sticky so you can just place it right
on without any glue and finally let's
add some final touch-ups and here we
have a super squishy tape ball why does
this remind me of a Chansey from Pokemon
hope you enjoyed